<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love Comes Down</title>
    <description>Love Comes Down is a children&#39;s book written by Natasha Frasch and illustrated by Avery Mefford. Site design by Preston Frasch.
</description>
    <link>http://lovecomesdown.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://lovecomesdown.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 13:10:43 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 13:10:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Inspiring Oneself</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently started a new job at a nursing home.  To be honest, it has been slightly overwhelming.  I’ve had this sort of job in the past, but I forgot how it felt to be among that much human suffering and loss concentrated in one place.  It’s not that it’s not a nice place, but at the end of the day, it’s not home.  Many are in wheel chairs; some are losing their ability to communicate.  They’ve lost parents, spouses, siblings, friends, sometimes children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second day of the job, I came home weary to my core, not that I had even done much work. Mostly I’d been on the computer doing online training and shadowing someone else who was doing the work, but emotionally, I might as well have run a marathon with a something on my back.  Preston, my husband, came home later that evening and asked about my day.  I think I sort of grunted.  To cheer me up, he showed me the Love Comes Down website he’s been working on (the one you are on now!) and  how to download the song.  As we listened to the song, I started to cry.  I can only love because God loved all of us first.  I can only suffer (or attempt to alleviate suffering) because Christ suffered first.  As the saccharine children’s song washed over me, it ministered to deep weary places in my heart.  It reminded me that as easy as the song was to sing, how very hard it is to live out and how much we need encouragement to do it!  It also reminded me too that this project (and every creative act) begins at some point to live its own life and do its own work apart from artist and sometimes to the artist.      We played it on repeat, and Preston held me.  And that is the story of how I inspired myself and made me cry.  Of course, it was not really me but the Truth setting me free, incrementally and incidentally through my own mouth, because He is humble and gracious like that.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 04:33:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lovecomesdown.org/elder/care/inspiration/2016/08/01/on-inspiring-oneself.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lovecomesdown.org/elder/care/inspiration/2016/08/01/on-inspiring-oneself.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>elder</category>
        
        <category>care</category>
        
        <category>inspiration</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting Finished to Get Started!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Although I have not been officially diagnosed by a professional author, I strongly suspect that I have a bad case of finishitis.  I have heard that it is a fairly common disease, especially among creative types.  It is characterized by starting projects and…not….quite…..being…….able……..to…..well, you get the idea.  If you are reading this right now, that means that I have taken a next step in my goal to self-publish a children’s book.  You have officially been drafted into my accountability/treatment team, and I am so glad you are here.  I hope perhaps if you have your own case of finishitis, it might inspire you too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four years ago, I wrote a short song called Love Comes Down.  One of my dearest friends, Avery Mefford, spent hours and hours illustrating vibrant scenes and characters, bringing the words to life.  Between getting married, adopting a daughter, and the many things life brings, we have been slowly, slowly plugging away at the next step which is getting published.  There are a surprisingly number of steps and discouragement seems to lurk around each corner.  That being said, in embarking on this project, a great number of gifts have already been given.  The cure for finishitis, I suspect will in the end be gratitude–gratitude to Avery, the many people who are helping this project, and, of course, to God who delights in using small things and weak people to show His faithfulness and love.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 20:00:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lovecomesdown.org/getting/finished/2016/07/28/getting-finished-to-get-started.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lovecomesdown.org/getting/finished/2016/07/28/getting-finished-to-get-started.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>getting</category>
        
        <category>finished</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
